<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>xuanjin</title>
    <link>https://xuanjin001.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on xuanjin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 12:10:32 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xuanjin001.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AI and What&#39;s Next</title>
      <link>https://xuanjin001.github.io/posts/mar_7_25/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 12:10:32 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xuanjin001.github.io/posts/mar_7_25/</guid>
      <description>AI has been in the spotlight ever since ChatGPT captured everyone&amp;rsquo;s attention. It evolutioned how we use the internet. For a lot of people, it changed how they write, how they approach to their daily work. The technology is there, so what&amp;rsquo;s next? What does the future hold from here?
As you start reading this, you may be wondering why we are revisiting this topic. People have been talking about AI and what it can do since 2023, and you might not want to hear about it in 2025 again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Rise of Artificial Intelligence: Transforming Our World</title>
      <link>https://xuanjin001.github.io/posts/the-rise-of-artificial-intelligence-11-4-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 11:16:22 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xuanjin001.github.io/posts/the-rise-of-artificial-intelligence-11-4-24/</guid>
      <description>Copilot (This article is created by copilot)
The Rise of Artificial Intelligence: Transforming Our World Artificial Intelligence (AI) has rapidly evolved from a futuristic concept to an integral part of our daily lives. But what exactly is AI, and how is it reshaping various sectors? What is Artificial Intelligence? Artificial Intelligence refers to the development of computer systems capable of performing tasks that typically require human intelligence. These tasks include recognizing speech, making decisions, and identifying patterns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AI...</title>
      <link>https://xuanjin001.github.io/posts/ai_11-3-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 16:06:30 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xuanjin001.github.io/posts/ai_11-3-2024/</guid>
      <description>AI has been a &amp;ldquo;hot&amp;rdquo; topic for about 2-3 years, ever since ChatGPT broke the internet lol, everything has been wrapped with AI. From couple years ago, there have been things claimed to be with AI, but they are not lol.
Is AI actually helping us or is it adding more trouble?
To answer that question, let&amp;rsquo;s go back and dig into what is AI.
You probably already hear the word AI have been throwing around a lot with machine learning, they go hand in hand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploy to GitHub Pages</title>
      <link>https://xuanjin001.github.io/posts/10_19_23/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 00:13:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xuanjin001.github.io/posts/10_19_23/</guid>
      <description>It took me a while to finish the deployment to &amp;ldquo;production&amp;rdquo; which is my github repo.
I would like to document what I was doing here so that I can refer to here later when I need to deploy again.
First of all, I swear there is a cache issue, every time I tried to run it locally, it is running as how I expected, but when I push the changes out to the github pages, it is still the older version, which has been driving me bananas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://xuanjin001.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xuanjin001.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello, my name is Xuan Jin, AKA Shirley.
I have been in the US since 2010, so I have been here for a while.
While you are reading this, in case you still cannot tell, I love gifs lol.
Currently, I am working for RSM as an architect. I see myself as a fixer there, wherever they need someone, I would jump in and help where I can. My specialties are:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My blog post project</title>
      <link>https://xuanjin001.github.io/posts/oct_14_2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 22:39:33 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xuanjin001.github.io/posts/oct_14_2023/</guid>
      <description>My blog post project Link to heading I have been writing on wordpress for a while now, on and off, I have been on wordpress for about 15 years. I still need to move everything from there to here. However, I am not waiting until I get everything sorted out before I start on something. I am going to get things started instead.
Wordpress is great, I can focus on the content, however, there are some things I don&amp;rsquo;t like about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>temas</title>
      <link>https://xuanjin001.github.io/categoria/temas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 23:21:18 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xuanjin001.github.io/categoria/temas/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sintaxe</title>
      <link>https://xuanjin001.github.io/categoria/sintaxe/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 23:21:06 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xuanjin001.github.io/categoria/sintaxe/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Códigos curtos</title>
      <link>https://xuanjin001.github.io/tags/shortcodes/_index.pt-br/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 11:51:36 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xuanjin001.github.io/tags/shortcodes/_index.pt-br/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://xuanjin001.github.io/about.cn-ch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xuanjin001.github.io/about.cn-ch/</guid>
      <description>Chinese version of about page
O Hugo faz o uso de vários projetos de código aberto incluíndo:
https://github.com/yuin/goldmark https://github.com/alecthomas/chroma https://github.com/muesli/smartcrop https://github.com/spf13/cobra https://github.com/spf13/viper O Hugo é ideal para blogs, sites corporativos, protfólio criativos, revistas online, aplicações de página única ou até sites com milhares de páginas.
O Hugo é para pessoas que querem cuidar do seu próprio site sem se preocupar com a configuração ambientes complicados, dependências e bancos de dados.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://xuanjin001.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xuanjin001.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>Follow me here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contato</title>
      <link>https://xuanjin001.github.io/contato/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xuanjin001.github.io/contato/</guid>
      <description>中文。。。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://xuanjin001.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xuanjin001.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description>This page is currently down&amp;hellip;
Xuan is working hard on fixing it!
Please reach out to the author for more details. You can reach out to her by going to her LinkedIn</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
