<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Xuan Jin on xuanjin</title>
    <link>https://xuanjin001.github.io/authors/xuan-jin/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Xuan Jin on xuanjin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:31:34 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xuanjin001.github.io/authors/xuan-jin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Latest Update April 24, 2024</title>
      <link>https://xuanjin001.github.io/posts/latest-update-apr-24-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:31:34 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xuanjin001.github.io/posts/latest-update-apr-24-2024/</guid>
      <description>I have been on this big big big projects for over a year now, it is like that&amp;rsquo;s my only life, nothing else, I felt like I was living under a rock for over a year. This project has been a mess from the start. Letting the client run the whole show was a mistake, and it was a mistake that I cannot reverse by the time I got onto the project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Jupyter With &#39;pipx&#39; </title>
      <link>https://xuanjin001.github.io/posts/mar_2_24/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 01:58:35 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xuanjin001.github.io/posts/mar_2_24/</guid>
      <description>It has been a while for me to write code now, it really depends on what I am currently doing. Ever since I was on this big project last Feb, I have been going non-stop basically. To the point that I really don&amp;rsquo;t want to look at any code related or any work related things, or even a computer screen after work. I really appreciate this opportunity though, I feel like throughout this project, I proved what I am capable of, before I know someone mentioned that &amp;ldquo;Is she ready?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploy to GitHub Pages</title>
      <link>https://xuanjin001.github.io/posts/10_19_23/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 00:13:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xuanjin001.github.io/posts/10_19_23/</guid>
      <description>It took me a while to finish the deployment to &amp;ldquo;production&amp;rdquo; which is my github repo.
I would like to document what I was doing here so that I can refer to here later when I need to deploy again.
First of all, I swear there is a cache issue, every time I tried to run it locally, it is running as how I expected, but when I push the changes out to the github pages, it is still the older version, which has been driving me bananas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrate Wordpress Part I</title>
      <link>https://xuanjin001.github.io/posts/10_20_23/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 00:04:59 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xuanjin001.github.io/posts/10_20_23/</guid>
      <description>I have been writing on wordpress for a long time, a long long long time. LOL. I had all kinds of things on there, it started out as a place I write my diaries, my feelings, the dates that went wrong, then I slowly transferred to professional contents. There are a lot of posts there in wordpress, I will need to export that out and format them to fit for the blog here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My blog post project</title>
      <link>https://xuanjin001.github.io/posts/oct_14_2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 22:39:33 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xuanjin001.github.io/posts/oct_14_2023/</guid>
      <description>My blog post project Link to heading I have been writing on wordpress for a while now, on and off, I have been on wordpress for about 15 years. I still need to move everything from there to here. However, I am not waiting until I get everything sorted out before I start on something. I am going to get things started instead.
Wordpress is great, I can focus on the content, however, there are some things I don&amp;rsquo;t like about it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
