<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on xuanjin</title>
    <link>https://xuanjin001.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on xuanjin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 16:06:30 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xuanjin001.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AI...</title>
      <link>https://xuanjin001.github.io/posts/ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 16:06:30 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xuanjin001.github.io/posts/ai/</guid>
      <description>AI has been a &amp;ldquo;hot&amp;rdquo; topic for about 2-3 years, ever since ChatGPT broke the internet lol, everything has been wrapped with AI. From couple years ago, there have been things claimed to be with AI, but they are not lol.
Is AI actually helping us or is it adding more trouble?
To answer that question, let&amp;rsquo;s go back and dig into what is AI.
You probably already hear the word AI have been throwing around a lot with machine learning, they go hand in hand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hunging....</title>
      <link>https://xuanjin001.github.io/posts/hunting_11_1_24/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 12:32:46 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xuanjin001.github.io/posts/hunting_11_1_24/</guid>
      <description>The job market has been a bit tough lately, even though you see there are a lot of position posted, but some of them may or may not be real tbh. A lot of layoffs were happening, there are people who just lost their job, there are people who lost their job for 5 months to 10 months, and there are people who just graduated from college. So many different talented people in the pool, and all of them are trying to get attentions from recruiters and hiring managers, it is hard to stand out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://xuanjin001.github.io/posts/projects_list/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 02:23:43 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xuanjin001.github.io/posts/projects_list/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploy to GitHub Pages</title>
      <link>https://xuanjin001.github.io/posts/10_19_23/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 00:13:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xuanjin001.github.io/posts/10_19_23/</guid>
      <description>It took me a while to finish the deployment to &amp;ldquo;production&amp;rdquo; which is my github repo.
I would like to document what I was doing here so that I can refer to here later when I need to deploy again.
First of all, I swear there is a cache issue, every time I tried to run it locally, it is running as how I expected, but when I push the changes out to the github pages, it is still the older version, which has been driving me bananas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My blog post project</title>
      <link>https://xuanjin001.github.io/posts/oct_14_2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 22:39:33 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xuanjin001.github.io/posts/oct_14_2023/</guid>
      <description>My blog post project Link to heading I have been writing on wordpress for a while now, on and off, I have been on wordpress for about 15 years. I still need to move everything from there to here. However, I am not waiting until I get everything sorted out before I start on something. I am going to get things started instead.
Wordpress is great, I can focus on the content, however, there are some things I don&amp;rsquo;t like about it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
